{
    "subject": "Lynn_Bari",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Sidney_Luft",
    "human_readable": "Lynn Bari is married to Sidney Luft.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885108470916748,
            "question": "Is Sidney Luft married to Lynn Bari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9872114062309265,
            "question": "Is there a known marriage between Lynn Bari and Sidney Luft?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9209616780281067,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Lynn Bari and Sidney Luft?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9206287264823914,
            "question": "To whom was Lynn Bari married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9043353199958801,
            "question": "Who is Lynn Bari married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8591009378433228,
            "question": "Lynn Bari's spouse is?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8519178032875061,
            "question": "Name the husband of Lynn Bari."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7269136309623718,
            "question": "What is the name of Lynn Bari's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7062764763832092,
            "question": "What is the name of Lynn Bari's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6272258162498474,
            "question": "Who is Sidney Luft?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lynn Bari is married to Sidney Luft.",
            "html": "yago_25113_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Lynn Bari's husband?",
            "html": "yago_25113_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Lynn Bari's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_25113_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the husband of Lynn Bari.",
            "html": "yago_25113_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25113_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25113_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25113_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25113_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25113_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25113_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25113_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25113_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25113_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25113_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nAccording to the provided context information, Sidney Luft and Lynn Bari were married for 8 years (document path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25113/re-ranker-msmarco/47.txt). Additionally, one of the documents mentions that Sidney Luft was the second husband of actress Lynn Bari (document paths: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25113/re-ranker-msmarco/14.txt and /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25113/re-ranker-msmarco/35.txt). Therefore, the information in the documents supports the triple \"Lynn Bari is married to Sidney Luft\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Lynn Bari is married to Sidney Luft.\" Specifically, multiple sources indicate that Sidney Luft and Lynn Bari were initially married in 1943 and divorced eight years later. This confirms their marriage relationship as stated in the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}